<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Hydra News</title>
    <link>CURRENTHOST</link>
    <description>News on the Hydra Larp Convention</description>
    <item>
      <title>Let's get ready for Hydra 2014</title>
      <link>CURRENTHOSTindex.php?pageName=news#38</link>
      <description>We are starting to get ready for Hydra 2014, so expect to see new News posts, photos, and games.&nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are going to make Hydra 2014 even bigger than previous years. There will be more games, greater variety and lots of fun. We will also have Tshirts and hopefully even mugs again for those who want them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Hydra</title>
      <link>CURRENTHOSTindex.php?pageName=news#5</link>
      <description>Hydra is a live-action roleplaying convention planned for Wellington. The third Hydra will be run over the weekend of 11 - 13 April 2014, at Brookfields Scout Camp in Wainuomata.Games are up now and game selection will be opened on 01 Feb 2013.&nbsp;Hydra was very successful last year, &nbsp;following the model of the &nbsp;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="http://www.nzlarps.org/chimera/index.html"&gt;Chimera Larp convention&lt;/a&gt;&nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game selection is live</title>
      <link>CURRENTHOSTindex.php?pageName=news#37</link>
      <description>You may now sign up for games on the&nbsp;registration&nbsp;page.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flagship: Dry Spell</title>
      <link>CURRENTHOSTindex.php?pageName=news#36</link>
      <description>Want to play in the flagship? &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://docs.google.com/spreadsheet/viewform?formkey=dDZJTF9zSGVWYUlkbm5STFlaZXlfNGc6MQ"&gt;Go fill in the questionnaire now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&lt;br&gt;Haven't made up your mind?&nbsp;&lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="http://hydra.nzlarps.org/index.php?pageName=game&amp;gameID=4"&gt;Read more about Dry spell&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-shirts!</title>
      <link>CURRENTHOSTindex.php?pageName=news#35</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are now taking&nbsp;T-shirt orders for this year's design.&nbsp;They will cost $30 each.&nbsp;This year's t-shirt looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img width="400" alt="" src="http://hydra.nzlarps.org/images/shirt2013.jpeg"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://docs.google.com/spreadsheet/viewform?formkey=dDlJZ29nOHpJRVVqV0Q5T2liQXhDaVE6MQ"&gt;Place your order now! &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>And we are off again</title>
      <link>CURRENTHOSTindex.php?pageName=news#34</link>
      <description>We are starting to get ready for Hydra 2013, so expect to see new News posts, photos, and games. &#13;
&#13;
We are going to make Hydra 2013 even bigger than 2012. There will be more games, greater variety and lots of fun. We will also have Tshirts and Mugs again for those who want them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just a month to go</title>
      <link>CURRENTHOSTindex.php?pageName=news#32</link>
      <description>Hi all&#13;
&#13;
Just a month to go and we will be into it.&#13;
&#13;
There are still a few spots left in a few games if you are interested in coming along to try a game&#13;
&#13;
Saturday 10AM -1PM And All that Jazz&#13;
Welcome to our 1920s gathering, enjoy socialising and intrigue, rub shoulders with Mobsters and PIs, High Society, journalists and flappers. How many skeletons do you have in the closet.&#13;
&#13;
Saturday 2PM – 5PM The Bell&#13;
The Bell is a science fiction suspense game inspired by The Fountain (Darren Aronofsky, 2006), Five-Twelfths of Heaven (Melissa Scott, 1985), Vacuum Flowers (Michael Swanwick, 1987) and the works of Cordwainer Smith. The Bell is intended to be an emotionally intense game that pushes moral dilemmas.&#13;
&#13;
Sunday 10AM – 1PM The Office Secret Santa&#13;
It’s the end of another long year, time to unwind, relax, and have a few quite ones at the office Christmas party. If only everything would stop going wrong.&#13;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last chance for preregistration</title>
      <link>CURRENTHOSTindex.php?pageName=news#29</link>
      <description>Game registration opens this Friday.  Which means that sometime this week, we will be locking the timetable and making a final decision on what games run when.  In doing so, we will effectively be making a decision on how many player spots there will be in the convention.  We will be making that decision based on the number of preregistrations, with a small provision for late registrations.&#13;
&#13;
In other words, if you want to be sure of playing, you need to &lt;a href="http://www.nzlarps.org/hydra/index.php?pageName=register</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diatribe Forums</title>
      <link>CURRENTHOSTindex.php?pageName=news#28</link>
      <description>Hydra now has a forum hosted on Diatribe.&#13;
&#13;
&lt;a href="http://www.diatribe.co.nz/viewforum.php?f=164</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transport and Food</title>
      <link>CURRENTHOSTindex.php?pageName=news#27</link>
      <description>As the Scout camp is a bit of the beaten track we recommend making sure you get food and supplies before you get to the camp. There will be food options on site, but there are no shops in walking distance.&#13;
&#13;
The Food Menu will be released when we have a better idea of numbers. Michelle has offered to cook meals for us.&#13;
&#13;
There is also a button for a transport option on the registration form. This will be used to indicate who needs a lift so we can try and organise some car pooling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armageddon and Going Live</title>
      <link>CURRENTHOSTindex.php?pageName=news#26</link>
      <description>So now we are live to the public with the launch in time for Armageddon in Auckland. So welcome to everyone checking out the site.&#13;
&#13;
Please be aware that things are likely to change and details to be tweaked as we go along. Games will be added, with at least 3 in every slot (depending on numbers), there are already more games on offer, they just haven't been added yet. If you find any mistakes or bugs please let us know.&#13;
&#13;
Game selection wont open until the new year, but if you register now, we will email you and advise you before it opens. And if you want to offer to run a game please feel free to contact us on &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:hydralarpconvention@gmail.com"&gt;hydralarpconvention@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;. And we can tell you what is required and what we need.&#13;
&#13;
We hope you can come along and have a fun time, and help us grow Larping in Wellington.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
