<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Hydra News</title>
    <link>CURRENTHOST</link>
    <description>News on the Hydra Larp Convention</description>
    <item>
      <title>Game selection is open</title>
      <link>CURRENTHOSTindex.php?pageName=news#30</link>
      <description>If you have already registered, just log in and go to the registration page to pick your games. If you haven't registered, what are you waiting for? &#13;
&#13;
If you have lost your user sign-in details, please use the &lt;a href="http://hydra.nzlarps.org/index.php?pageName=contact"&gt;contact form&lt;/a&gt;. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last chance for preregistration</title>
      <link>CURRENTHOSTindex.php?pageName=news#29</link>
      <description>Game registration opens this Friday.  Which means that sometime this week, we will be locking the timetable and making a final decision on what games run when.  In doing so, we will effectively be making a decision on how many player spots there will be in the convention.  We will be making that decision based on the number of preregistrations, with a small provision for late registrations.&#13;
&#13;
In other words, if you want to be sure of playing, you need to &lt;a href="http://www.nzlarps.org/hydra/index.php?pageName=register</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diatribe Forums</title>
      <link>CURRENTHOSTindex.php?pageName=news#28</link>
      <description>Hydra now has a forum hosted on Diatribe.&#13;
&#13;
&lt;a href="http://www.diatribe.co.nz/viewforum.php?f=164</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transport and Food</title>
      <link>CURRENTHOSTindex.php?pageName=news#27</link>
      <description>As the Scout camp is a bit of the beaten track we recommend making sure you get food and supplies before you get to the camp. There will be food options on site, but there are no shops in walking distance.&#13;
&#13;
The Food Menu will be released when we have a better idea of numbers. Michelle has offered to cook meals for us.&#13;
&#13;
There is also a button for a transport option on the registration form. This will be used to indicate who needs a lift so we can try and organise some car pooling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armageddon and Going Live</title>
      <link>CURRENTHOSTindex.php?pageName=news#26</link>
      <description>So now we are live to the public with the launch in time for Armageddon in Auckland. So welcome to everyone checking out the site.&#13;
&#13;
Please be aware that things are likely to change and details to be tweaked as we go along. Games will be added, with at least 3 in every slot (depending on numbers), there are already more games on offer, they just haven't been added yet. If you find any mistakes or bugs please let us know.&#13;
&#13;
Game selection wont open until the new year, but if you register now, we will email you and advise you before it opens. And if you want to offer to run a game please feel free to contact us on &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:hydralarpconvention@gmail.com"&gt;hydralarpconvention@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;. And we can tell you what is required and what we need.&#13;
&#13;
We hope you can come along and have a fun time, and help us grow Larping in Wellington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venue</title>
      <link>CURRENTHOSTindex.php?pageName=news#25</link>
      <description>Brookfeld Outdoor Education Centre, RD1, &#13;
562 Moores Valley Road, Wainuiomata, Lower Hutt&#13;
There will be transport arranged from Wellington to the venue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flagship LARP</title>
      <link>CURRENTHOSTindex.php?pageName=news#20</link>
      <description>Progress has been made on finding writers for the flagship LARP on the Saturday night. More details to come&#13;
&#13;
</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
